var stQuiz= [
  {
    'question': `What does the 'T' stand for in James T Kirk?`,
    'options': ['Talented', 'Thelonius', 'Tiberius', 'Thermopoli'],
    'answer': 3
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the color of Vulcan's blood?",
    'options': ['white', 'yellow', 'green', 'purple'],
    'answer': 3
  },
  {
    'question': "What is Zefran Cochran famous for inventing in Star Trek?",
    'options': ['Warp Technology', 'Artifical Intelligence','The Transporter' , 'The Food Replicator'],
    'answer': 1
  },
  {
    'question': "How long was the Enterprise's mission?",
    'options': ['2 years', '5 years','10 years' , '7 years'],
    'answer': 2
  },
  {
    'question': "What groundbreaking event occured in Star Trek that had not occured before?",
    'options': ['An interacial kiss.', 'The first Prime Time Science Fiction Show.','A multi-ethnic cast.' , 'Two men kiss'],
    'answer': 1
  },
  {
    'question': "What is of primary importance to Kiligons?",
    'options': ['Personal Hygeine', 'Honor','Love' , 'Victory'],
    'answer': 2
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the state  James T. Kirk calls home?",
    'options': ['Iowa', 'Kentucky','California' , 'Texas'],
    'answer': 1
  },
  {
    'question': "Spock is half Vulcan and half _______?",
    'options': ['Andorian', 'Woman','Romulan' , 'Human'],
    'answer': 4
  },
  {
    'question': "Who create Star Trek?",
    'options': ['H.G. Wells', 'Gene Roddenberry','Glen Larson' , 'Willian Kelly'],
    'answer': 2
  },
  {
    'question': "What is the Hull designation on the Enterprise?",
    'options': ['USS-1965', 'THX-1138','UFP-Enterprise', 'NCC-1701'],
    'answer': 4
  }
]
